Be yourself and you can be anything
Katy Perry: Part of Me is a documentary, music film directed by Dan Cutforth.
Giving fans unprecedented access to the real life of the music sensation, Katy Perry: Part of Me exposes the hard work,
dedication and phenomenal talent of a girl who remained true to herself and her vision in order to achieve her dreams.
Featuring rare behind-the-scenes interviews, personal moments between Katy and her friends, and all-access footage of rehearsals, choreography, Katy’s
signature style and more, Katy Perry: Part of Me reveals the singer’s unwavering belief that if you can be yourself, then you can be anything.
Self, played by Katy Perry.
Self, played by Shannon Woodward.
Self, played by Rachael Markarian.
Self, played by Mia Moretti.
Self, played by Glen Ballard.
Self, played by Adam Marcello.
Katy Perry: Part of Me (advertised as Katy Perry: Part of Me 3D) is a 2012
American 3D autobiographical documentary concert film about Katy Perry.
It was directed by Dan Cutforth and Jane Lipsitz and released in the
United States, Canada, the UK and Ireland on July 5, 2012.
The film follows Perry through her California Dreams Tour while providing an insight into the singer's
journey through stardom and detailing various aspects of her professional and personal life.
It is interspersed with various moments of emotional
weight and deep significance to Perry.
Produced on a budget of $13.2 million, the film has grossed nearly $33 million worldwide, making it the
second highest grossing music concert film ever by a female artist, while ranking fifth overall.
Part of Me currently sits as the eleventh highest grossing documentary in U.S.
box-office history.
It received positive reviews for successfully conveying an effective understanding of Perry as an individual, while also
garnering praise for her willingness to allow audiences an up-close appreciation of her personal life.